Guide to the Carole Hyatt Papers 1947-2006 (bulk, 1980s-1990s) MS 3105
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Audiotapes, 1975-2003, undated; 8 Linear feet
  - Subseries III.A. Audiotapes, Digitized, 1975-2003, undated; 6 Linear feet (457 cassette tapes in 6 boxes; 1.09 terabytes of digital files)
    - Light, Donald (1 tape/2 files), 1991 January 22 (Box T6, Item 441)
      "On Chicago and Brandeis." The Chicago School title, which was used for the digital file name, comes from a post-it in the cassette box. Several tapes were identified somehow during digitization as related to "Chicago School Study Interviews." But there is no indication on the tapes or their case themselves that they relate. It is possible that the linking documentation was lost during the digitization process. The tapes so identified are items 401, 441, 442, 443, 444, 445, 446, and 447.
    - Hyatt, Carole and Noriko [Sakayori] (1 tape/2 files), 1991 April 30 (Box T1, Item 012)
      "Yesterday" "Smile shows the life" with handdrawn Asian language characters. [On index, re: radio interviews]
    - Flynn, Mary (1 tape/2 files), 1992 August 28 (Box T1, Item 068)
      "Wisdom, side 1; fraction, side 2"
    - Dictation (1 tape/2 files), 1992 September 18 (Box T1, Item 027)
      "Dictation." Other annotations on the label suggest this might be the third side of a dictation.
    - Hadley, David (1 tape/2 files), 1993 May 6 (Box T1, Item 035)
      The tape label includes various notes and dates, some struck through or obscured. Includes a reference to Hadley, as well as "Taos--6/92"
    - Aspen Women's Group (1 tape/2 files), 1994 February 13 (Box T2, Item 094)
      Both sides labeled. [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - Women's Group (1 tape/2 files), 1994 February 16 (Box T1, Item 028)
    - Berger, Sally (1 tape/2 files), 1994 February 18 (Box T2, Item 088)
      [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - Daniels, Deborah; Daniels, Delmar (1 tape/2 files), 1995 January 17 (Box T1, Item 007)
      Deborah on Side A (1st file): "Odyssey" "Fulfilling wk life." Delmar on Side B (2nd file): "Host" "Odyssey." [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - Salzman, Bert (1 tape/2 files), 1995 June 2 (Box T2, Item 102)
      There are multiple notes on the labels. It appears certain that the main, perhaps only, content relates to Salzman re: "money matters." Reference on the label is also made to "Dictation 8/14/90. II 7/7/93."
    - Hyatt, Carole. Interview (1 tape/2 files), 1995 June 4 (Box T1, Item 057)
      "KPIX Radio. San Francisco, CA"
    - Finley, Pat (1 tape/2 files), 1995 July 9 (Box T1, Item 066)
      "Wisdom"
    - Karen Steele Show. Guest: Carole Hyatt, author of "Lifetime Employability" (3 tape/6 files), 1995 August 1 (Box T1, Item 060-062)
      "8/1/95, 7-8pm" "WALE - Talk Radio 990, Providence RI." Tape from radio station. Appears to be 3 copies rather than 3 tapes comprising one interview.
    - New York City Women's Group (1 tape/2 files), 1995 September 10 (Box T1, Item 030)
      "Romance / Marketing." [Per index, re: marketing yourself for love]
    - New York City Women's Groups (1 tape/2 files), 1995 September 11 (Box T1, Item 031)
      "Side 3 and 4"
    - Reinisch(?), June (1 tape/2 files), 1995 December 5 (Box T2, Item 097)
      "Wisdom. 2 sides"
    - Dean and Donna (1 tape/2 files), 1996 January (Box T1, Item 008)
      "Montana ranchers. 70s." [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - Focus Group, Ship Odyssey (1 tape/2 files), 1996 January 17 (Box T1, Item 069)
    - Herwood, Carol (1 tape/2 files), 1996 January 17 (Box T2, Item 104)
      "ex-nun. Retired. Wants to be [?]. Odyssey." [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - John (host), Tuscon, Ariz. (1 tape/2 files), 1996 January 19 (Box T2, Item 092)
      Both sides are labeled "Short interview someplace on tape" meaning the item could be anywhere on the two files created from the tape
    - Viers, Del and Jane (1 tape/2 files), 1996 January 19 (Box T2, Item 093)
      "2 sides. Retirement." [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - Hirsch, Jack and Ruth (1 tape/2 files), 1996 January 21 (Box T1, Item 006)
      "80s. Vitality. Learners. Retired in 50s. Full 2 sides." [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - Brandt, Lois (1 tape/2 files), 1996 February (Box T2, Item 087)
      "San miguel(?). Wisdom" [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - Dallas Women (1 tape/2 files), 1996 August 15 (Box T1, Item 034)
      "Marketing app. 75 min. 2 sides." [Per index, re: marketing yourself for love]
    - Pascuzzi, Dominic and Carolyn (1 tape/2 files), 1996 September 19 (Box T1, Item 009)
      "Computer supervisor to turkey ranchowners." [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - Waite, Carol Cox (1 tape/2 files), 1996 October 4 (Box T1, Item 040)
      "Time management" "1-1/2 sides"
    - Rust, Langbourne (1 tape/2 files), 1997 January 17 (Box T1, Item 039)
      "Money Book" "He roller coaster income/entrepreneurial. She steady academic."
    - Clarke, Rebecca. "Completely Clarke" concert (1 tape/2 files), 1999 September 25 (Box T5, Item 348)
      Program for the concert, held at Brandeis University, is in the cassette container. This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Corbato, Emily (1 tape/2 files), 2002 May 9 (Box T5, Item 346)
      "Photos from the Ukraine." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. That list indicates the full title of the presentation on this tape is "Vsevo Khoroshovo: All Good Things: Photographs from the Ukraine." The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Narratives on Mothering (1 tape/2 files), 2002 May 13 (Box T5, Item 345)
      This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. That list indicates that this tape is of a colloquium featuring the speakers Lauri Aumansky, Evelyn Murphy, Marcie Tyre, Tracey Hurd, Mei-Mei Ellerman, Ruth Nemzoff, and Emily Corbato, under the full name "A Mother's Day Celebration: Narratives on Mothering." The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Goldstein, Nance (1 tape/2 files), 2002 June 4 (Box T5, Item 344)
      "Where are the women?" This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Rosen, Ellen (1 tape/2 files), 2002 September 5 (Box T6, Item 455)
      "Ellen Rosen on Walmart. Talk and Q&A". Side 1 includes the talk (45 minutes) and question period (15 minutes). Side 2 continues with questions for 19 minutes. The label also indicates there is "Song: George Dalaras, last 2 min" but not clear which side it is on. This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Porter, Susan (1 tape/2 files), 2002 September 10 (Box T6, Item 452)
      "Gendered Expectations: Orphans and Apprenticeship in Antebellum New England." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Ahmed, Fauzia (1 tape/2 files), 2002 September 19 (Box T6, Item 451)
      "Are Progressive Men the Key Ingredient in Low-Income Bangladesh?" This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Gadon, Elinor (1 tape/2 files), 2002 October 8 (Box T6, Item 449)
      "The Secular Israeli Woman: A Transgressive and Heretical Spirit." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Bouvard, Marguerite (1 tape/2 files), 2002 November 12 (Box T6, Item 453)
      "Art, Illness & Spirituality." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Mirkin, Marsha (1 tape/2 files), 2002 November 14 (Box T6, Item 454)
      "Loss & Healing: A Psychological Reading of the Book of Ruth." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Mark, Elizabeth Wyner (1 tape/2 files), 2002 November 21 (Box T4, Item 318)
      "Servant-Mothers of Israel." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Kahne, Hilda (1 tape/2 files), 2002 December 12 (Box T4, Item 317)
      "A climate of recession: Economic implications for poor single mothers." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Murphy, Evelyn (1 tape/2 files), 2002 December 17 (Box T4, Item 316)
      "Why women will never be paid like men unless we act." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Weston, Kath and Cash, Debra (1 tape/2 files), 2003 January 30 (Box T5, Item 319)
      "Advantages to academics of joining NWU." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Shtern [or Stern], Ludmila (1 tape/2 files), 2003 February 6 (Box T5, Item 329)
      "Wanderlust: A Reading." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Ellerman, Mei-Mei (1 tape/2 files), 2003 February 27 (Box T4, Item 315)
      No subject noted on label. This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Trafficking in Nepal (1 tape/2 files), 2003 March 5 (Box T5, Item 347)
      This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. That list indicates the presenter on this tape is Anuradha Koirala. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Barnett, Roz [Rosalind] (1 tape/2 files), 2003 March 6 (Box T6, Item 450)
      "Working Parents Sweat It Out When Their Children Are Unsupervised After School." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Munn, Rachel (1 tape/2 files), 2003 March 11 (Box T6, Item 448)
      "Memory and the City: Berlin Passages." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Berg, Mary (1 tape/2 files), 2003 March 13 (Box T5, Item 394)
      "Contemporary Cuban Women Writers." This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Mother's Day Celebration (1 tape/2 files), 2003 May 13 (Box T5, Item 327)
      This is one of 21 tapes that were identified in the papers as being recordings of "scholars' presentations"; see the folder "Lists & notes re: tapes" at Box 9, folder 20. According to that list, the name of the colloquium was "The Mother in Us: Telling Experiences and Making Connections", featuring Nurit Eini-Pindyck, Mei-Mei Ellerman, Deborah Klotz Paris, Marcie Tyre, and Ruth Nemzoff. The 21 tapes were digitized; these are items 315, 316, 317, 318, 319, 327, 329, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 394, 448, 449, 450, 451, 452, 453, 454, 455.
    - Abady, Josephine; Berkshire Theater Festival (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 041)
      Abady labeled as "1/2 side." [On index, re: radio interviews]. Berkshire labeled as "Side III"
    - Ambrose, Baron & Mickie (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T2, Item 080-081)
      On tape 1: "Side A & B. Sept. 16." On tape 2: "Side 3." [On index re: winning couples]
    - Anthony, Julie (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 178)
    - Appleman, Herb and Dee (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T4, Item 265-266)
      Labeled on three sides of two tapes. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Astro[?] Reading (1 tape/1 files), undated (Box T6, Item 417b)
      On second side of tape only. First side was taped over, at least in part, by the Roxanne Mankin material.
    - Atlas, Larry (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 180)
      On side 2, label reads: "tape blank for 3/4 upfront. Tape starts 3/4 in" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Babcock, Barbara (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 229)
      Side 2: "1/2 side" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Backes, Arlene (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 267)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. "1-1/2 hrs. gd corporate takeover, bureaucracy, unemployment, being 50, spiritual, moving as kid, self-confidence." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Balthazar, Carol (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 262)
      "Bio at end of tape." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Barber, Ben (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T3, Item 231-232)
      Labeled on both sides of first tape. On second tape (item 232): "Side 3, 1/2 tape" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Barlow (Rodgers), Betsy (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 256)
      Labeled on both sides of the tape. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Barrie [or Barry], Barbara (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T2, Item 122-123)
      3 sides. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Bazelmans, Genevieve (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 254)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Beling, Stephanie (M.D.) (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 125)
      "Side 1: 1/2 tape only" "Side 2: 1/2 in." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Berenbeim, Glenn (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T3, Item 204-205)
      2nd tape, side 3: "1/4" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Bergen, Polly (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 203)
      Labeled on both sides. Side 2 notes "listen for double ending" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Berman, Norman (Dr) (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T4, Item 248-249)
      "NYU". Labeled on 3 sides of two tapes. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Bickford, Jewelle (4 tapes/8 files), undated (Box T3, Item 199-202)
      Tape 1 (item 199): "Faulty[?] machine." Tape 2 (item 200): Side 1: "Interview 2"; Side 2: "5 min." Tape 3 (item 201): "Side 3" on first side, no label on reverse. Tape 4: "5 min on [illegible] of Jewelle Bickford." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Blanca, Rosa (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 206)
    - Blythe, Bruce (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 116)
      "Ford. Diversification planning"
    - Boland, Jack (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 243)
      "Church of Unity." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Brademus [Brademas], John (Dr) (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 207)
      Labeled on both sides. Side 2: "1/2 side" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Brav [Brau?], Peter (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 208)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. See also item 182 for possible conclusion.
    - Brav [Brau?], Peter; Buckingham, Richard (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 182)
      Side 1: "Brav [or Brau] "5 min. Richard Buckingham, partner law firm." Side 2 label refers only to Buckingham. See item 208 for more Peter Brau, possibly opening. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Brown, Angela; Weaver, Nancy (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T2, Item 095-096)
      Tape 1: Side 1 (first file) holds the Brown interview; during digitization the file name was incorrectly rendered as Paracen, Ansela". Side 2 (second file) holds the first part of the Weaver interview. Tape 2 (third and fourth files) holds rest of Weaver. [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - Burns, Mike (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T4, Item 240-241)
      "Harvard counselor." Labeled on all 4 sides of 2 tapes. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Bushnell, Nolan (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T3, Item 183-184)
      2nd tape label refers to "Reconstructed" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Butera, Robert; Johnston, Jim (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T3, Item 197-198)
      First tape (item 197): Both names are on the side 1 label; only Butera is on the side 2 label. Second tape (item 198) is labeled on the first side only: "Side 3, 1/4 tape" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Campanis, Paul (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 328)
    - Canttrella, Marcia (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T3, Item 195-196)
      The name also appears on the labels as Cantrelli and the index as Canterelli. When the tapes were digitized the name was rendered in the file names as Cantarella. The two tapes are labeled on 3 of the 4 sides. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Carter, Ron (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 193)
      Side 2: "1/2 side". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Carter, Vicki (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 194)
      Side 2: "3/4". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Chicago School Study Interviews (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 447)
      Several tapes were identified somehow during digitization as related to "Chicago School Study Interviews." But there is no indication on the tapes or their case themselves that they relate. It is possible that the linking documentation was lost during the digitization process. The tapes so identified are items 401, 441, 442, 443, 444, 445, 446, and 447. This tape 447 and its case are unlabeled and are possibly blank.
    - Cohen, David (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 043)
      "WTTW" noted on both sides of tape.[On index, re: radio interviews]
    - Cook, Pat (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 166)
      "Ward Howell. Search-partner-[illegible]" Labeled on both sides. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Cooney, Gerry [Gerald]; Rappaport, Dennis (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T3, Item 186-187)
      Labels on first tape (item 186): Side 1: "Dennis Rappaport, 1/2 side; Gerry Cooney public remarks (5 mins)." Side 2: "Gerry Cooney, Side 1 (may begin in middle?)." Tape 2 is labeled with Cooney's name on both sides. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - David (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T2, Item 119-120)
      Tape 1 (item 119) is labeled only as "David." Tape 2 (item 120) is labeled "David, cont'd. Trigger" on first side and "David. (Stuck)" on second side." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - DeMarco, Toni (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 131)
      Labeled on both sides. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Detroit Men's Group (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 056)
    - Dixson, J.B. (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 135)
      "Burroughs Corp." Labelled on both sides, side 2 is noted as "full side." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Doherty, Mary (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 222)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. Name appears on labels as "Reginald Herzslinger" and as "Reggie Herslinger." During during digitization, the name was renderd for file naming as "Sonya Herzlinger." A Regina with a similar last name also is found in some of the paper documents. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Edwards, Ned (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 139)
      Labeled on both sides of tape; Side 2 is "1/2 side" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Egon (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 442)
      Several tapes were identified somehow during digitization as related to "Chicago School Study Interviews." But there is no indication on the tapes or their case themselves that they relate. It is possible that the linking documentation was lost during the digitization process. The tapes so identified are items 401, 441, 442, 443, 444, 445, 446, and 447. For this tape 442, the label on side 1 of the tape itself reads only "Egon".
    - Elman, Lee (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 140)
    - Erikkila, Dan (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 216)
      The tapes are unlabeled, but the name Dan Erkkila (variant spelling from that on tape) was assigned during digitization. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]